Ever wondered what happens when unstoppable forces meet immovable objects?
Brace yourself for the top five shocking ship bridge collisions.
Number five, the Lake Charles disaster,
where a tanker lost control and rammed into a busy bridge, causing chaos.
Number four takes us to the Sunshine Skyway Bridge,
where a sudden storm led to a tragic clash, altering the bridge's history forever.
At three, Sydney Harbor witnessed the MV Test Bank's blunder,
a spectacle that halted traffic and hearts alike.
Second place goes to the Big Bayou Connaught tragedy,
a barge collision that resulted in one of the deadliest train disasters in US history.
And at number one, the heart-stopping moment a colossal ship brought down
Genoa's Mirandi Bridge, a calamity that shook the world.